# Elahe Jamshidi Araghi

# elijam1608@gmail.com | Contact No: +61 420585600

Sydney, NSW-2066

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elahe-jamshidi

Github: <a href="https://github.com/Eli-33">https://github.com/Eli-33</a>

# **Career Summary**

An individual who love challenges and is always inclined to fulfill all the tasks on time and with professional manner. Already hold 9+ years of experience in teaching English to different age group people. Took a challenge to change my career and move in to web development field. Have to my credit full stack web development course from boot camp organized by University of Sydney & Trilogy Pty Ltd.

#### Technical Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, API

# **Projects/Applications**

## Website

**Entertainment Library** 

- Application will display information and recommendation about any artists, books, movies typed by using the Taste Dive API, and also using the Wikipedia API to display general information about the chosen artist.
- Developer in a group of three.
- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, API Keys
- Built the contact and our team page of the website using the HTML & CSS.
  Created the readme profile, worked on the API key (Taste Dive) and JavaScript.
- GITHUB LINK: <a href="https://github.com/DCLucas95/Project-1-Recommendations">https://github.com/DCLucas95/Project-1-Recommendations</a>
- WEBSITE LINK: https://dclucas95.github.io/Project-1-Recommendations/

### **Professional Experience**

- Teacher Assistant (TA) at Hayat Universal business school, Qatar (February 2018- June 2019)
- English Language Teacher at BH.Mehrega. INST (March 2009 –June 2017)
  Iran, Tehran,
- Teaching IELTS course at Aryam College (November 2016 March 2017)
  Iran, Tehran
- Administrative Assistant at Elia Co. (May 2016 August 2016) Iran, Tehran
- Commercial and Sales Expert at Atie Sanaat CO. (Feb 2014 May 2016) Iran, Tehran
- Commercial Sales Expert at Foolad Sazan LTD (Sept 2013 Nov2014) Iran, Tehran

- English Language Teacher at Kanoon Farhangi Amoozesh Ghalamchi (July 2014 - September 2014) Iran, Tehran
- English Language Teacher at Shokooh English Institute (Sept 2011 Sept 2013) Iran, Tehran
- English Translator at Red Lantern Co (March 2012 September 2012) Iran,
  Tehran
- English Language Teacher & supervisor at Tehran Oxford Limited (March 2008 September 2011) Iran, Tehran
- English Language Teacher at Noor Institute (May 2007 September 2008) Iran, Tehran.

### Education

- Boot Camp in University of Sydney- Certificate in Full Stack Web Development, August 2020 February 2020.
- Aryanpour School of Culture and Education, Tehran (Iran)
  - Writing course for IELTS / Vocabulary course for IELTS, Jan 2016 -Mar 2016
- Garmsar Azad university, Garmsar (Iran)
  - o Master of Arts (M.A.), 2013 2015
  - Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language
- Azad University of Rodehen, Tehran (Iran)
  - o Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), 2006 − 2010
  - Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language
- Kish Language Institute, Tehran (Iran)
  - o Advance Level, 2006 2007
  - o Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language

Elahe Jamshidi Araghi hereby declare that the above-furnished details are true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date: 05/10/2020

Place: Sydney, Australia (Elahe Jamshidi Araghi)